# Assignment: Write a program that first reads in the name of an input file, followed by two strings representing the lower and upper bounds of a search range. The file should be read using the file.readlines() method. The input file contains a list of alphabetical, ten-letter strings, each on a separate line. Your program should output all strings from the list that are within that range (inclusive of the bounds).

file_input = input()
string1 = input()
string2 = input()

file = open(file_input)
lines = file.readlines()

for line in lines:
	if (line.strip() >= string1) and (line.strip() <= string2):
	    print(line.strip())
